Well, then, we've got a delivery for you.
Are you swearing?
No, I'm not.
Good night.
I see you're in.
The delivery is in.
Yes, sir.
What's going on?
I'm so flustered.
You've got teeth in your teeth. Are you okay?
Dash? As fast as you can?
He made a little dash for it.
That's how they come out.
Everybody's out.
Hello.
Good evening.
First of all...
I'm sure you've seen a lot of the people who were recently turned into Ohmakiuchi Devil.
I'm sure you've seen a lot of it.
Thank you very much.
So, well, we've talked a little bit about that today, but I'm sure you've all sent us your impressions, etc.
I'm sure you've all sent us your impressions and comments, and we've had a lot of them on the show.
I've read a lot of the photos and texts that you sent in, and I'm going to make a new turnaround.
I'd like to make a new start.
We've already taken a step toward the future!
Yes, that's right.
I'll start with a few words of wisdom.
Wow, here it comes!
Um...
Keanu Reeves, the famous actor.
Yes.
Well...
He has this type.
He's from Canada.
Did you write this again?
You always write about Keanu Reeves.
You wrote about Keanu Reeves last time.
I just realized he's two years older than me.
I don't really feel it, but...
I'm two years older than you, so when Keanu Reeves was in the third grade, I was in the first grade.
Oh, wow, he's your senior.
I don't know why Keanu and I go to the same school.
Yeah, Keanu Reeves said that.
May I? Yes, sir.
If you can make a woman smile.
That's the most beautiful thing you've seen on this planet.
That's great!
I don't know if I'm supposed to say this, but really, Mr. Kianolive, you're such a gentleman.
No, but really, Mr. Keano Reeves is such a gentleman.
He's a gentleman. He's really cool.
I'm sure he means it. He really means it.
He really means it. Yes, he does.
When I start saying things like this, it's a little bit like I'm laughing, isn't it?
You say things like this because you want a laugh, right?
No, you are not. You are saying it from the bottom of your heart.
It's like a normal conversation.
That's right.
Just by watching his behavior, you can feel it.
It's amazing.
Well, you know, even Sapon is more of a "Quijano" type.
Refreshing.
It's presumptuous of me.
I'd never lie to you.
I won't.
You won't?
No, I wouldn't.
I'll never lie.
Do they think you're lying?
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I just want a clean heart.
That's right.
A clean heart.
Pitch white.
Yes, sir.
Now that I've said that...
I just tweaked it a little.
But I'm sure he has a pure heart.
Right?
Let's give it a little more oomph.
Yes, let's get some momentum going.
We've got to get a running start.
What's your favorite food?
Crab cream croquettes.
Yes, sir.
That's what I'm talking about.
Very nice.
The crab cream truck is here.
Really?
Crab cream truck?
Yes!
Mr. Pichiponpon Yokosuka.
Thank you very much
The name is cute!
The other day, I went into a Western-style restaurant.
I was wondering which one to eat from the many dishes on the menu.
I thought, "Oh, this is the one that Sarpong likes, I can keep up with the level!
So I decided on the crab croquette.
So I decided to have the crab croquette.
Masashi!
Looks delicious!
You can't see the inside, but there's probably cream in it.
Crab croquettes are not often croquettes only with crab, right?
That's for sure!
The cream is probably
Looks delicious!
The shape is also interesting.
Indeed.
It looks like something like a cucumber.
I don't know why.
It looks like slime.
It's not bale-shaped.
Of course it is. It's usually like this.
I see.
Interesting.
It looks like it's full of crabs.
Where is it?
Looks delicious.
This place...
But... you know, lately I've been hearing a lot about catnip.
I have catnip, by the way.
I have a cat tongue, too.
I'm not a cat person.
Not a cat
Not a cat.
I see.
I am hot.
So, for example, when you eat something like this, it comes out really hot, doesn't it?
That makes us a little uneasy, but the Knot's tongue can go down with a gulp.
Yes, you're right.
I see.
That's why we don't know what it feels like.
Yes, we break the knots and let the little ones cool down before eating them.
I see.
When you crack it open, a lot of steam comes out, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
And while watching the steam, we would take a short break and then eat it after a while, just as if it were a hot spring.
After a while, you see how it looks.
Yes, that's right.
After a long time...
I've been doing that since I was little.
I've been doing that since I was a little kid, so I don't feel like eating something like this in one bite.
I don't feel like eating it in one bite.
That's right.
I've never eaten it in one bite.
Heh...
You crack it open, let it cool, and say "Onsen-da!" for a while, and then take a bite.
It's a little bit like "onsen da-da!
Ma-ma's... Ma-ma's...
Mamama's?
Yes.
So that's what it means.
Yes, I see.
Well, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Looks delicious.
I love it.
I haven't had this in a while.
I want to eat it.
I want some!
It's so cute!
I want some.
Like Winnie the Pooh.
I want to eat it.
I want some!
Let's serve lots of honey!
I want to eat it!
It's so cute.
It's so cute!
So cute!
By the way, we just talked about food.
Yes.
How about this?
What?
Why?
Well, it's something like udon.
Udon is just one word...
Yes...
Some are so-called "Kishimen" and others are...
And others...
There's regular udon, Sanuki style udon, and soft udon.
There are soft and hard ones.
Yes.
There are wide udon noodles, aren't there?
So we had a chance to try some of those udon noodles.
Tokyo
Richard Thank you very much. 26 years old.
The first one.
Master Sarpon, thank you very much.
The other day I went to eat udon in Ginza and I found the widest udon I've ever had!
The noodles were so wide that I had a hard time slurping them down, but the taste was excellent.
I'm sure you can find this kind of udon in Ginza, but it's mainly common in local cuisine.
Yes, yes, yes!
This one.
Amazing!
It doesn't look like udon.
Looks delicious.
Looks like cheese.
Like paper.
Looks delicious
Looks like it's going to be served on top!
I love wide udon noodles like this.
I see.
Me too.
I can't get enough of Kishi Noodles.
I wonder why.
The texture is totally different.
It's wider.
I can't get enough of it.
Looks delicious!
I see... I see...
Udon noodles with a wide range of texture
That's what it's called
Well, well, well...
That's how it is, sir.
Let's see...
Like this
For now, this block is
Yes.
It's good, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Let's go for a while.
One time.
Bye-bye.
Shall I close it like this?
Yes.
Well, well, well.
That's how it goes, sir.
Well, we'll see you next time, won't we?
If you have any letters to send...
I'd like you to send them to me again.
I'm sure you will.
Well...
I'm sorry to say...
Well, you know...
I'm going to start a live broadcast from here.
I mean...
The pictures you all sent me...
The outside?
I mean, we're inside.
I mean, we're inside, we're rehearsing.
It's hard to know what's going on outside, isn't it?
That's right.
Like, were there a lot of people like this outside?
Yes.
People in costumes...
Or, "There were customers like this.
Everyone sent me pictures of what they saw.
Thank you for sending us the pictures.
Thank you very much.
It's nice to know.
Yeah, it was...
It was fun.
I didn't know it was this much fun.
No, it's... it's... it's really great.
I'm so glad.
It's like one big festival.
I'm so glad
It's like...
Well.
So how was it, by the way?
How was everyone?
Yeah.
Do you want to write down some thoughts?
Sure.
First of all...
Um...
Mr. Tak Minqi...
Takminchi?
Devil's Charge.
I received this as a "thank you" for the fun we had at the Devil's Charge in Odate!
Wow!
Thank you so much!
Takminchi is so generous!
And Mr. 99...
Hmm?
Mr. Kujukushiki.
He gave us that silent spacha.
What's that?
It's a devil charge with no title.
It's a Devil's Charge with no text.
Oh, really?
Like a silent phone call?
That's right.
A mute phone call.
I'm sorry.
Like you don't want to say your name?
I guess so.
That's cool.
I won't say much.
Yo.
Period drama.
Jidai Gekijo?
Yo.
Jidai-Gekijo.
Yes.
Yes, ma'am.
It's Emma.
I'm so glad.
The performance by Sarpong was wonderful. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
And... your sister Cam looked great in her part-time job.
She's cute. It suits her.
She was a bit of a delinquent. She was carrying an iron pipe.
She had an iron pipe, too, but she was a bit of a punk.
He's so proud of himself. He couldn't hide it.
I see... some of you didn't get the Master's flip-flop.
I'll give you as many as you want. I'll give you mine without saying a word.
But you know what? See you next year... next year for the Keano Reeves movie.
The film of Mr. Keano Reeves. See you next year.
Another film by Keano Reeves. See you next year.
Quiano Reeves' movie, next year, maybe, if we do it again.
Quiano Reeves, I'd really like to give it to someone like that.
We'd really appreciate it if you could fill out a survey for us.
Is there something going on?
Yes, there is. I think they're looking for people to fill out a survey.
Yes, we'd love to have it. Yes, we'd love to have it.
Please, please, please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please, please.
Mr. Yuhi from Zadar has also received a deville charge for his great success in Odate Deville.
That means he came from Zadar Kashiwa.
That's right.
Kashiwa is not that far away.
Kashiwa is on the Chiyoda Line?
Yes, yes, yes.
Is it far?
Chiyoda Line or Joban Line.
Yes, it's a long way.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's what I was thinking.
But it's pretty far.
It's farther than I thought.
I'd like to hear Zadar's opinion.
It took him this long to get here.
How long does it take?
Even now, there's the Shonan Shinjuku Line.
Like the Ueno Tokyo Line.
Cherry Blossom Front Line
I liked the Sakura Zensen.
Thank you very much.
Cherry blossoms
cherry blossom
fetters
I heard you won the flip of the dgp of "Futsun"!
I'm sure that Momoshiki-san and Shiki 100 will be back next year with a big prize.
I am sure that Momoshiki-san and Shiki-san 100 will be back next year with their level charge.
And Tamamin, you also had the best Ookan level from the beginning to the end of the new opening.
I'm very excited about the new opening.
I'm excited about the new opening and I don't know about you, but I'd like it to happen again this year, not next year.
The dibel-charge is coming in fast and furious!
I'm sure the dibber charge just keeps on coming... and it's so cool to see a guy with a Concours d'Elegance on his head... and not a clunker.
I'm glad we were able to fire the last ganda on our return, Don.
I'm so glad I was able to do it.
I'm glad you were able to do it too!
I'm waiting to shop for a movie....
I'm waiting for the movie.
Thank you, Boo Boo!
Thank you very much.